{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Driveway Power Washing Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/62497/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62497,"taskName":"Driveway \u0026 Concrete - Power Wash","taskDescription":"Power Wash a Driveway or Concrete","xmTaskDescriptor":"Driveway Power Washing Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"powerwash power wash concrete driveway pressure","textMessagingName":"Driveway Powerwash","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically used to clean concrete, masonry \u0026 other surfaces.  This category is for powerwashing only.  Note separate category for powerwashing \u0026 applying sealant.","rolloverShortDesc":"Cleaning with a high-pressure sprayer.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Power Wash a Driveway or Concrete.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated pressure washing services in your area.","htmlTitle":"Driveway Power Washing Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Pressure Washing Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Driveway \u0026 Concrete Power Washing","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Driveway Power Washing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Powerwashing Need","urlName":"Driveway-or-Concrete-Power-Washing","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Driveway \u0026 Concrete Power Washing Services in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"powerwash power wash concrete driveway pressure cement","emcCategoryOid":-14980,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9090,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62497/":{"taskOID":62497,"originalTaskOID":62497,"setID":9090,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5399,"questionDisplayText":"Why Power Washing is Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need power/pressure washing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove oil or grease ","answerDisplayText":"Remove oil or grease ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5175,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","answerDisplayText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5167,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","answerDisplayText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove mold or moss","answerDisplayText":"Remove mold or moss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5399,"questionDisplayText":"Why Power Washing is Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need power/pressure washing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove oil or grease ","answerDisplayText":"Remove oil or grease ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5175,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","answerDisplayText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5167,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","answerDisplayText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove mold or moss","answerDisplayText":"Remove mold or moss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove oil or grease ","answerDisplayText":"Remove oil or grease ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5175,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","answerDisplayText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5167,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","answerDisplayText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove mold or moss","answerDisplayText":"Remove mold or moss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}